<article>
<preamble> Boudin-Torres-2006.pdf </preamble>
<titre> A Scalable MMR Approach to Sentence Scoring for Multi-Document Update Summarizationring  </titre>
<auteur> Florian Boudin \ and Marc El-Bèze \onring  </auteur>
<abstract> Abstract redundancy with previously read documents (history) has to be removed from the extract. A natural way to go about update summarizationtory) has to be removed from the extract. would be extracting temporal tags (dates, elapsedy) has to be removed from the extract. times, temporal expressions...) (Mani and Wilson,y) has to be removed from the extract. 2000) or to automatically construct the timeline,y) has to be removed from the extract. from documents (Swan and Allan, 2000). Theseline,y) has to be removed from the extract. temporal marks could be used to focus extracts ony) has to be removed from the extract. the most recently written facts. However, most recently written facts are not necessarily new facts. Machine Reading (MR) was used by (Hickl etmost recently written facts are not necessarily new facts. al., 2007) to construct knowledge representationscently written facts are not necessarily new facts. from clusters of documents. Sentences containing “new” information (i.e. that could not be inferred by any previously considered document) are selected to generate summary. However, thisg “new” information (i.e. that could not be inferred by any previously considered document) highly efficient approach (best system in DUCisg “new” information (i.e. that could not be inferred by any previously considered document) 2007 update) requires large linguistic resources.“new” information (i.e. that could not be inferred by any previously considered document) (Witte et al., 2007) propose a rule-based system.“new” information (i.e. that could not be inferred by any previously considered document) based on fuzzy coreference cluster graphs. Again,“new” information (i.e. that could not be inferred by any previously considered document) this approach requires to manually write the sentence ranking scheme. Several strategies remaining on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed from history were used by (Boudin and TorresMoreno, 2007) to minimize history’s redundancy.ining on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed (Lin et al., 2007) have proposed a modified Maximal Marginal Relevance (MMR) (Carbonell andy.ining on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed Goldstein, 1998) re-ranker during sentence selection, constructing the summary by incrementallying on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed re-ranking sentences.anker during sentence selection, constructing the summary by incrementallying on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed In this paper, we propose a scalable sentencelection, constructing the summary by incrementallying on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed scoring method for update summarization derivedction, constructing the summary by incrementallying on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed from MMR. Motivated by the need for relevantvedction, constructing the summary by incrementallying on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed novelty, candidate sentences are selected according to a combined criterion of query relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed dissimilarity with previously read sentences. Theng to a combined criterion of query relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed rest of the paper is organized as follows. Section 2to a combined criterion of query relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed rest of the paper is organized as follows. Section 2to a combined criterion of query relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed We present S MMR, a scalable sentencelows. Section 2to a combined criterion of query relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed scoring method for query-oriented update summarization. Sentences are scoredof query relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed thanks to a criterion combining query relevance and dissimilarity with already ready relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed documents (history). As the amount of relevance and dissimilarity with already ready relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed data in history increases, non-redundancyevance and dissimilarity with already ready relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed is prioritized over query-relevance. Wecyevance and dissimilarity with already ready relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed show that S MMR achieves promising results on the DUC 2007 update corpus.ready ready relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed show that S MMR achieves promising results on the DUC 2007 update corpus.ready ready relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed 1how that S MMR achieves promising results on the DUC 2007 update corpus.ready ready relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed 1how that S MMR achieves promising results on the DUC 2007 update corpus.ready ready relevance and on post-processing redundancy removal techniques have been suggested. Extracts constructed  </abstract>
<biblio> References  </biblio>
</article>
